Here, you can see as a result of applying Bayes' rule for the localization posterior.
ここでは ローカライズされた事後確率にベイズルールを適用した結果を見ることができます
To define the likelihood term,
尤度を定義するには t での状態と観測値を変え、
we swapped the state and the observation at t,
またすべての別の状況を
and also take into account all other conditions.
考慮します
The prior and the normalizer are also
事前確率と正規化項も、
conditioned by the previous observations or controls and the math.
前回の観測値またはコントロールと数学で調整されます
It is totally fine here to condition
制御（変数）や、観測値やマップのような任意のランダムな変数に
base rule on arbitrary random variables like the controls,
ベイズルールを適用することは
like our observations, and the map.
全く問題ないです
And please, take a look at this.
そして これを見てください
If you remove the additional conditions in the posterior,
後ろの方の追加条件を取り除くと
you would end up exactly with the general Bayes' formula.
一般的なベイズの式と全く同じになります
Recall the likelihood terms observation model,
観測ベクター t の確率分布を表す 尤度項観測モデルを思い出してください
which describes the probability distribution of the observation vector,
それは 観測値ベクター
t. Another assumption that a state x_t are previous observations,
t ある状態 ｘt が前回の観測群であり
are controlled, and the map are given.
その値はコントロールされたものであり、地図情報も与えられた、と別の仮定をします
The prior is called a motion model.
事前確率はモーションモデルと呼ばれます
It is a probability distribution of x_t given all observations from one to t minus one.
それは提供された 1 から t-1 までのすべての観測値で提供された xt の確率分布です
All controls and the math take into account that
すべてのコントロールと数学は 現在の観測値が
no current observations are included in the motion model.
モーションモデルに含まれないことを考慮します
To simplify the normalization part,
正規化部分を簡単にするには
we define the normalizer as Ether.
正規化群をエーテルとして定義します
Ether is one of the original normalization term and this term is a sum of
η（イータ）は元の正規化項の1つで この項はすべての可能な状態にわたる
the product of the observation and the motion model over all possible states, x_t_i.
観測と運動モデルの積 xt-1 の合計です
This also means you only have to define
またこれは 信念を推定するには
the observation and motion model to estimate the beliefs.
観測値とモーションモデルだけを定義しないといけないということです
So, let's discuss these two terms more in detail.
そのため これらの 2 つの用語について詳しく話していきます
What you see here is again the definition of the motion model.The problem here
ここで示すのは またモーションモデルの定義です ここでの問題は
is that we have no information where the car was before at time T minus one.
時間 T-1 の前に車があった場所の情報がないということです
This means, no information about the previous state, x_t minus one.
これは 以前の状態 x_t -1 の情報がないということです
Now, my question is,
では 質問は
what kind of rule or law can we use which will help us here?
ここで手助けするために どんな種類の規定や公式を使用できるかです